<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Support Andrew on WeisGarden</title><link>https://weismind.com/support/</link><description>Recent content in Support Andrew on WeisGarden</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://weismind.com/support/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Support Andrew</title><link>https://weismind.com/support/support-andrew/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://weismind.com/support/support-andrew/</guid><description>&lt;p>Creating websites, content, and learning takes up an immense amount of time, but doing this kind of work makes me feel awesome and the challenge is a pretty good reward. However, being challenged and feeling awesome doesn&amp;rsquo;t pay a whole lot - it pays nothing in fact. Freelancing isn&amp;rsquo;t as lucrative as it once was since everyone is now a &amp;ldquo;vibe coder&amp;rdquo; and finding work as software developer is challenging at the moment.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Creator Platforms</title><link>https://weismind.com/support/creator-platforms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://weismind.com/support/creator-platforms/</guid><description>&lt;p>You can contriute on these particular creator platforms - I try my best to keep them up to date with content and projects I&amp;rsquo;m working on so you can find my work there if it is not on my digital garden here.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="ko-fi---geauxweisbeck4">Ko-Fi - GeauxWeisbeck4&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>You can find creations, posts, and more on Ko-Fi. Subscribe or make a one time donation.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href='https://ko-fi.com/Z8Z2D853F' target='_blank'>&lt;img height='36' style='border:0px;height:36px;' src='https://storage.ko-fi.com/cdn/kofi5.png?v=6' border='0' alt='Buy Me a Coffee at ko-fi.com' />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="buy-me-a-coffee---geauxweisbeck4">Buy Me A Coffee - GeauxWeisbeck4&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Basically the same thing as Ko-Fi, except it&amp;rsquo;s competitor.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Direct Donation</title><link>https://weismind.com/support/direct-donation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://weismind.com/support/direct-donation/</guid><description>&lt;p>And the most simple and effective way to help is donating directly to Cash App and Venmo. I&amp;rsquo;m looking to add other ways to donate, but donating via these methods is the most helpful way to give. I say that because there is no fee that we get charged (platforms take like 5-10% sometimes) and it goes directly into our pocket so we can feed ourselves and save up for housing.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Publications</title><link>https://weismind.com/support/publications/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://weismind.com/support/publications/</guid><description>&lt;p>These are publications I create content on and they typically have ways you can sponsor me, subscribe to my content, or even sometimes just visiting and sharing these pages will help me earn money. If you can&amp;rsquo;t afford to help out with a subscription or donation, definitely sharing these with your network has a huge impact.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="substack---the-weismind-newsletter--geaux-code-newsletter">Substack - The WeisMind Newsletter &amp;amp; Geaux Code Newsletter&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>These are both brand spanking new newsletters that are just about to drop.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>