<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio on GeauxWeisbeck4.dev</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolio on GeauxWeisbeck4.dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Andrew&#39;s Digital Garden</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/andrews-digital-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/andrews-digital-garden/</guid>
      <description>This is my special corner of the internet in which you will find ideas, stories, notes, bookmarks, and many other things that I think are useful. It took me a while to publish my public workspace on the web, but it is finally here after finding the perfect template to publish my site with - thank you to Varun for sharing this open source project.&#xA;I am using the Hugo Digital Garden Theme theme created by Varun A P, a very talented front-end engineer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SupaSnake.js</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/supasnake-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/supasnake-js/</guid>
      <description>SupaSnake.js is a remake of the all-time classic &amp;ldquo;Snake&amp;rdquo; game, where the user controls a super hungry snake who is on a mission of a lifetime, trying to consume as manny &amp;ldquo;apples&amp;rdquo; as he possibly can. Little does he know that with each apple he happily devours, he is one apple closer to his death!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tar Heel Dev Studio</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/tar-heel-dev-studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/tar-heel-dev-studio/</guid>
      <description>Tar Heel Dev Studio Website I started Tar Hee Dev Studio back at the end of 2021 when I first started looking for developer jobs. What started out as a brand to help market my freelance services has become my primary source of income and my most valuable work experience as a developer.&#xA;Tech Stack Astro.js Static Site Generator Tailwind CSS Typescript Project Status This project is my main source of income so it is always a work in progress.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
